dominos.com 2013-10-16

# Legal Privacy Policy - Domino's Pizza, Order Pizza Online for Delivery - Dominos.com

Safeguarding your privacy and the security of your personal information is important to us. Please take a few minutes to read the following policy so that you understand how we treat your personal information. As we continuously improve and expand our services, this policy might change, so please check it periodically. If you have questions about our privacy policy, please use the form on our [Contact Us](https://info.dominos.com/dominos_pizza/contact.nsf/frmContact?openform) page.

## Purpose

Domino's Pizza has adopted this Privacy Policy in order to inform you of its policies with respect to information collected from the online and mobile web site (collectively, the "Web Sites") and our tablet and smartphone applications (the "Application" or collectively the "Applications"). Your use of the Web Sites or Applications constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and your consent to the practices it describes.

## Personally Identifiable Information

Personally Identifiable Information is any information that concerns you individually and would permit someone to contact you, for example, your name, address, telephone/fax number, email address or any information you submit to dominos.com or the Applications that identifies you individually.

The Web Sites or the Applications will not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless you provide it.

Therefore, if you do not want us to obtain any personally identifiable information about you, please do not submit it to us.

You can visit and browse the Domino's Pizza Web Sites and the Applications without revealing personally identifiable information about yourself, but not all functions will be available to you. You may also choose to disclose personally identifiable information about yourself, which may be maintained as described below. The Web Sites and the Applications may collect personally identifiable information about you by methods such as the following:

  * Registration Forms - If you are offered the opportunity to enter a promotion, to become a registered user of dominos.com, or to opt-in to receive Domino's Pizza information through another site or the Applications, you must apply by filling out the registration form on the site or the Application. This form requires certain personally identifiable information that may include, without limitation, your name, email address, postal address, telephone number, areas of interest, product usage, credit/debit card number(s) with associated expiration date(s), CVV and billing zip code(s), and/or a unique individual password.
  * Transactions and Activity - If you become a registered user or if you conduct transactions through the Web Sites or an Application, we will collect information about the transactions you engage in while on the Web Sites or Application and your other activity on the site or Application. This information may include, without limitation, areas of the Web Sites or Application that you visit, transaction type, content that you view, download or submit, transaction amount, payment, and billing information as well as the nature, quantity and price of the goods or services you exchange and the individuals or entities with whom you communicate or transact business.
  * Email and other voluntary communications - You may also choose to communicate with us through email, via our Web Sites, via the Applications, by telephone, in writing, or through other means. We collect the information in these communications, and such information may be personally identifiable.

## Non-Personally Identifiable Information

When you visit the Domino's Pizza Web Sites and Applications, like when you visit most other web sites and applications, certain anonymous information about your visit is automatically logged, which may include information about the type of browser you use, the server name and IP address through which you access the internet (which identifies the company providing you internet access and general geographic information), the date and time you access the site, the pages you access while at the Domino's Pizza Web Sites, and the internet address of the web sites, if any, from which you linked directly to the Domino's Pizza site or Application. This information is not personally identifiable.

## Information Use

Domino's Pizza may use the personally identifiable information collected through its Web Sites or Applications primarily for such purposes as:

  * helping to establish and verify the identity of users;
  * opening, maintaining, administering and servicing users' accounts or memberships;
  * processing, servicing or enforcing transactions and sending related communications;
  * providing services and support to users;
  * improving the Web Sites, including tailoring it to users' preferences;
  * providing users with product or service updates, promotional notices and offers, and other information about Domino's Pizza and its affiliates;
  * responding to your questions inquiries, comments and instructions;
  * protecting our systems from fraud and unlawful access;
  * maintaining the security and integrity of its systems.

Domino's Pizza uses the anonymous browsing information collected automatically by its servers primarily to help it administer and improve its Web Sites and Applications. Domino's may also use aggregated anonymous information to provide information about its Web Sites and Applications to potential business partners and other unaffiliated entities. Again, this information is not personally identifiable.

## Disclosure of Information

Domino's Pizza does not provide personally identifiable information to unaffiliated third parties for their use in marketing directly to you. Domino's Pizza may use unaffiliated companies to help it maintain and operate its Web Sites, Applications, payment processing, or for other reasons related to the operation of its business, and those companies may receive your personally identifiable information for that purpose. These companies may only use such personally identifiable information for the purpose or performing those functions and may not use it for any other purpose. Domino's may also disclose personally identifiable information about you in connection with legal requirements, such as in response to an authorized subpoena, governmental request or investigation, or as otherwise permitted by law.

## Children's Privacy

The Web Sites and Applications are directed toward and designed for use by persons aged 13 or older. Domino's Pizza will not approve applications of, or establish or maintain registrations for any child whom Domino's knows to be under the age of 13. Domino's Pizza does not solicit or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If Domino's nevertheless discovers that it has received personally identifiable information from an individual who indicates that he or she is, or whom Domino's Pizza otherwise has reason to believe is, under the age of 13, Domino's will delete such information from its systems. Additionally, a child's parent or legal guardian may request that the child's information be corrected or deleted from our files by requesting this via our [Contact Us](https://info.dominos.com/dominos_pizza/contact.nsf/frmContact?openform) page.

## "Cookies" and Advertisers

The Domino's Pizza Web Sites' and Applications' server, or the servers of companies that are used to operate the Web Sites and Applications, may place a "cookie" on your computer or store data in your computer browser in order to allow you to use the Web Sites and Applications and to personalize your experience. A "cookie" is a small piece of data that can be sent by a web server to your computer, which then may be stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies and browser storage allow us to recognize your computer while you are on our Web Sites and Applications and help customize your online experience and make it more convenient for you. Cookies and browser storage are also useful in allowing more efficient log-in for users, tracking transaction histories and preserving information between sessions. The information collected from cookies and browser storage may also be used to improve the functionality of the Web Sites and Applications.

Most web browser applications (such as Microsoft Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Firefox and Apple Safari) have features that can notify you when you receive a cookie or prevent cookies from being sent. If you disable cookies, however, you may not be able to use certain personalized functions of the Web Sites.

### Retargeting and Online Behavioral Advertising

Retargeting is a way to use non-personal information to remind you on other websites that you were browsing Domino’s Web Sites previously with the goal to bring you back to our site. Domino's may use the non-personal information collected on its Web Site for online behavioral advertising purposes including retargeting and to customize ads to you when you visit other (non-Domino's) sites. If you wish to opt-out of this process, click the OBA logo on our banner advertisements. You will be directed to an opt-out page where you'll be able to select your data preferences.

Domino's has engaged third parties, including advertising providers such as DoubleClick, to collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. The information collected on Domino's behalf by these third parties does not contain your name, address, email address, or any other personally identifiable information.

These companies typically use cookies, pixel tags / web beacons, and similar technologies to analyze your usage of our sites. These third parties collect, and share with us, as we may request, non-personally identifiable information during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you, including such web site usage information about visits to our sites, measure and research the effectiveness of our advertisements, track page usage and paths followed during visits through our sites, help us serve relevant Internet banner advertisements on our sites and on other sites, and track use of our Internet banner advertisements and other links from our marketing partners' sites to our sites. To see further information about these third party cookies on dominos.com, and opt out as you choose, see the descriptions and links below. To continue to accept cookies and browse normally on dominos.com, click [here](http://www.dominos.com/)

Types of cookies and tags on our sites:

  * Functionality: Used to remember your preferences for using the sites and for facilitating transactions such as purchases.
  * Performance or Analytics: Used to anonymously measure site activity to improve visitor experience.
  * Targeting: Used to display information and offers that specifically interest you.

### Opt out

In the section below, we provide links to resources for opting out of different types of cookies.

[Click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) to visit the Network Advertising Initiative site or [click here](http://www.aboutads.info/) to visit and learn about the Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising, behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, as provided by our third party vendors, including: Adara Media, Blue Kai, Casale Media, Invite Media, Media Mind, Microsoft Advertising, x+1.

[Click here](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/?hl=en&hl=en) to opt out of the Google Network (Doubleclick, AdSense, Analytics).

[Click here](http://kb.webtrends.com/support/solutiondetail.aspx?Id=50140000000a79PAAQ) to opt out of Webtrends analytics.

In addition, our European users may [click here](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/) learn more information about their online choices at www.youronlinechoices.com and to opt-out of this type of advertising, including by these vendors: Xaxis, LLC.

## External Links

The Domino's Pizza Web Sites and Applications may contain links to other web sites not maintained or related to Domino's Pizza. These links are provided as a service to users and are not sponsored by or affiliated with the Web Sites, Applications, or Domino's Pizza. Domino's Pizza has not reviewed any or all of the sites hyper-linked to or from the Web Sites or Applications and is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other web sites. The links are accessed at the user's own risk, and Domino's Pizza makes no representations or warranties about the content, completeness or accuracy of these links or the sites hyper-linked to the Web Sites or Applications. Web sites that are accessible by hyperlinks from the Domino's Pizza Web Sites or Applications may use cookies. Domino's Pizza encourages you to read the privacy statements provided by other web sites before you provide personally identifiable information to them. Domino's Pizza does not implicitly endorse third-party sites hyper-linked to the Web Sites or Applications.

## Security

Domino's Pizza maintains physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to help guard personally identifiable information. If transactions are offered on the Web Sites or Applications, transaction information is transmitted to and from Domino's in encrypted form using industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) connections to help protect such information from interception. Domino's restricts authorized access to your personal information to those persons who have a legitimate purpose to know that information to provide products or services to you and those persons you have authorized to have access to such information. Credit/debit card number(s) you elect to provide on file as part of your online profile for use when placing an order through the Domino's Pizza Web Sites or Applications will be tokenized and maintained in an encrypted format by a third party provider to further lower any risk. It is your responsibility to protect the integrity of your own account by keeping your account name and password safe. Please be aware, however, that any email or other transmission you send through the internet cannot be completely protected against unauthorized interception.

## Choice/Opt-Out

In order to provide service to you, we may send you communications related to your transactions, security or the administration of the Web Sites or Applications. From time to time, Domino's Pizza and its affiliates may also wish to send you other messages or updates about our Web Sites, Applications, Domino's Pizza, our affiliates, or their promotions and other activities. If you do not wish to receive non-transaction/security related communications from Domino's Pizza and its affiliates, please send an email containing your request via our [Contact Us](https://info.dominos.com/dominos_pizza/contact.nsf/frmContact?openform) page.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

Domino's Pizza reserves the right to modify or supplement this policy at any time. If a material change to the terms of this policy is made, Domino's will post a notice on its homepage and a link to the new policy.

## Contacting Us

If you have questions about this privacy statement, the information practices of Domino's Pizza or your dealings with our Web Sites or Applications, please use the link on our [Contact Us](https://info.dominos.com/dominos_pizza/contact.nsf/frmContact?openform) page.

## Gift Cards

For terms of use and privacy policy information on Gift Cards, please click here.

## Revision Date

This policy was last updated February 8, 2013.

***** New Password:

**Note:** Use at least 8 characters.

***** Confirm Password:

**Heads Up!** Use at least 8 characters.

***** Yes. I would like to receive e-mail offers from Domino's Pizza 

***** Yes. I agree to the Terms of Use and I am 13 or older 

***** Confirm Password:

**Heads Up!** Use at least 8 characters.

Keep Me signed in 

Legal Notice Get faster access to your profile features such as recent orders and saved addresses. 

You will have the opportunity to select "Keep me signed in" checkbox when you create a Pizza Profile or sign in to your existing Pizza Profile for a quicker ordering experience. By checking this box, you allow Domino's to provide you with a more personalized experience in which you will be greeted by your first name and presented with (i) your Easy Order™, (ii) a list of your recent orders and (iii) information about your local store. When you select "Keep me signed in", you will remain signed in to your Pizza Profile on that particular computer or device for up to six months or until you select the "sign out" link or clear your computer's or device's cookies. Although you are signed in to your Pizza Profile account, you will be prompted for your password if you attempt to perform a sensitive action such as modifying the personal information in your Pizza Profile account or completing an order using a stored credit card. If you change your mind about remaining signed in, simply select the "sign out" link to deactivate this feature.  
NOTE: To prevent others from accessing your Pizza Profile account, Domino's does not recommend the use of this feature on any public or shared computer or device.

House Apartment Business Campus/Base Hotel Dormitory Other

Save this address to my Pizza Profile 

***** Address Nickname:

**Example:** My home, my studio, school, etc.

***** Delivery Instructions:

**Example:** Gate code, ring the door bell, etc.

Make this address my primary address 

Visa Mastercard AMEX Discover JCB Diner's Enroute

Save my credit card for faster future ordering 

***** Credit Card Nickname:

**Example:** My Visa, Corporate Card, etc.

Make this card my primary card 

Congratulations $[firstName]! Your Pizza Profile has been created.
